Joshua Logan Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Production File, 1903-1989 (Box 96-129)
  - Middle of the Night
    - Financial papers
      - Investors, 1955-1956
      - Statements, 1956-1957, 1986-1987
    - General correspondence, 1955-1957
    - Legal papers, 1955-1957
    - Other productions, 1957-1958
    - Publicity, 1955-1957 (Box 114)
    - Reviews, 1956
    - Tickets, 1956
    - Working papers, 1955-1956 See also Oversize
  - Miscellany, 1940-1983, undated
  - Miss Liberty
    - Financial papers, 1948-1949
    - Legal papers, 1949
    - Publicity, 1949
  - Miss Moffat (1974 production)
    - Casting, 1972-1975, undated, (3 folders)
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1972-1973, undated
      - General, 1972-1975, undated
      - Investors, 1974-1975, (3 folders)
      - Royalties, 1973-1975, undated
      - Statements, 1974
    - General correspondence
      - 1964, May 1971-Sept. 1972
      - Oct. 1972-Nov. 1975, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - Legal papers, 1972-1987, (5 folders)
    - Publicity, 1972-1981
    - Reviews, 1974
    - Working papers
      - Performance, 1972-1974, undated, (2 folders)
      - Script, 1965-1974
  - Miss Moffat (1983 production) (Box 116)
    - Casting, 1981-1982, 1987
    - Financial papers, 1982-1983
    - General correspondence, 1980-1983
    - Legal papers, 1982-1987
    - Publicity, 1982-1983
    - Reviews, 1983
  - Mister Roberts (play)
    - Casting, 1948, undated
    - Financial papers
      - Investors, 1950-1953
      - Royalties, 1948-1986, (2 folders)
    - General correspondence, 1948-1955
    - Legal papers, 1947-1989, undated, (2 folders)
    - Other productions
      - Burt Reynolds Dinner Theatre, 1979-1980
      - General, 1948-1983, undated
      - London, Eng., 1949-1950
      - Seventh Army Special Services, 1951
    - Publicity, 1947-1950 See also Oversize
    - Reviews, 1948-1950
    - Working papers
      - Script, undated
      - Technical, 1947, undated
  - Mister Roberts (film) (Box 117)
    - Financial papers, 1954-1966
    - General correspondence, 1950-1956, undated
    - Legal papers, 1953-1963
    - Miscellany, 1955
    - Publicity, 1955-1963
    - Working papers, script, 1954-1955, undated
  - Mister Roberts (television)
    - Financial papers, 1964-1966
    - General correspondence, 1965
    - Legal papers, 1962-1976
    - Publicity, 1984
  - Morning's at Seven
    - Legal papers, 1939, 1985
    - Publicity, 1939
    - Reviews, 1939
  - Mr. President
    - Casting, 1962, undated
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1962-1966
      - General, 1963-1966
      - Royalties, 1965-1976
      - Statements, 1962-1963, undated
    - General correspondence, 1962-1963
    - Legal papers, 1962-1964
    - Publicity, 1962-1963 See also Oversize
    - Reviews, 1962
    - Tickets, 1962
    - Working papers
      - Performance, 1962
      - Script, 1961-1963, undated
      - Technical, 1961-1962
  - Nightclub act (Box 118)
    - Casting, undated
    - Financial papers, 1977-1985, undated, (2 folders)
    - General correspondence, 1976-1985, undated
    - Legal papers, 1977-1982
    - Publicity, 1977-1986, undated, (2 folders)
    - Reviews, 1977-1985
    - Working papers
      - Performance, 1977-1985, undated
      - Script, 1977-1985, undated
      - Technical, 1985, undated See also Oversize
  - Nothing but the Truth
    - General correspondence, 1978
    - Miscellany, 1978
    - Publicity, 1978
  - On Borrowed Time
    - General correspondence, 1938, 1984, (2 folders)
    - Legal papers, 1937
    - Publicity, 1938
    - Reviews, 1938
  - Paint Your Wagon
    - Casting, 1968
    - Financial papers, 1952, 1968-1970
    - General correspondence, 1968-1971
    - Legal papers, 1967-1968 (Box 119)
    - Publicity, 1968-1979, undated, (2 folders)
    - Reviews, 1969
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1968, undated
      - Technical, 1967-1969
  - Parrish
    - Legal papers, 1958-1959
    - Publicity, 1958-1959
  - Picnic (play)
    - Casting, 1951-1953, undated
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1952-1953
      - Investors, 1952-1962
      - Statements, 1953-1955, (3 folders)
    - General correspondence, 1952-1954
    - Legal papers, 1951-1954, 1981
    - Other productions, 1953-1954, 1986 (Box 120)
    - Publicity, 1952-1954, 1969 See also Oversize
    - Reviews, 1953
    - Tickets, 1953
    - Working papers
      - Performance, 1953
      - Script, 1951-1954, undated
      - Technical, 1952-1954 See also Oversize
  - Picnic (film)
    - Casting, 1953-1956, undated
    - Financial papers, 1955-1964
    - General correspondence, 1952-1956, 1964, 1987, (2 folders)
    - Legal papers, 1953-1958, (2 folders)
    - Publicity, 1955-1956
    - Reviews, 1956
    - Working papers
      - Performance, undated
      - Script, undated
      - Technical, 1955
  - Princeton University, Princeton, N.J., Triangle Club productions, 1928-1980
  - Ready When You Are, C. B.
    - Casting, 1964-1965, undated
    - General correspondence, 1956, 1964, undated
    - Legal papers, 1964-1965, 1973
    - Publicity, 1964 (Box 121)
    - Reviews, 1964
    - Working papers, script, 1964
  - Rip Van Winkle
    - Casting, undated
    - Financial papers, 1976
    - General correspondence, 1975-1976
    - Legal papers, 1975-1976
    - Miscellany, 1976
    - Other productions
      - Philadelphia, Pa., 1976
      - Washington, D.C., 1976
    - Publicity, 1975-1976
    - Research material, undated
    - Reviews, 1976
  - Sayonara
    - Casting, 1954-1956
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1953-1957
      - General, 1956-1969, undated
      - Statements
        - Aug. 1958-June 1959, (2 folders)
        - July 1959-July 1970, (4 folders) (Box 122)
    - General correspondence, 1953-1959, (3 folders)
    - Legal papers, 1953-1973, (3 folders)
    - Publicity, 1954-1960, undated, (3 folders) (Box 123)
    - Research material, 1954-1956, undated
    - Reviews, 1957-1958
    - Tickets, 1954-1958
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1954-1957
      - Technical, 1954-1958, undated
  - South Pacific (play)
    - Casting, 1948-1952, undated
    - Financial papers
      - Berman, Milton, 1949-1979
      - General, 1948-1958
      - Investors, 1949-1984
      - Royalties, 1949-1970
      - Statements, 1949-1969
    - General correspondence, 1948-1967
    - Legal papers
      - Authors' credit line, 1951-1986, (3 folders)
      - General, 1949-1987
    - Miscellany, undated
    - Other productions (Box 124)
      - Armed services, 1950-1955
      - Australia and Japan, 1951-1954
      - Europe, 1950-1987
      - London, Eng., 1950, 1973-1988
      - United States, 1950-1988, (2 folders)
    - Publicity
      - Commercial enterprises, 1949-1951
      - General, 1948-1977, undated See also Oversize
    - Reviews, 1949
    - Tickets, 1949-1950
    - Working papers, performance, 1949-1950, undated
  - South Pacific (film)
    - Casting, 1956-1957, (3 folders)
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses, 1957-1958
      - General, 1957-1981
      - Investors, 1957-1987
      - Royalties
        - 1957-1969
        - 1970-1984, (2 folders) (Box 125)
      - Statements, 1959-1986
    - General correspondence, 1956-1987, (2 folders)
    - Legal papers, 1956-1987, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1959
    - Publicity, 1957-1984, undated, (2 folders)
    - Reviews, 1958
    - Working papers
      - Performance, undated
      - Script, 1957, undated
      - Technical, 1956-1957
  - Stars in Your Eyes
    - Legal papers, 1938
    - Publicity, 1939
    - Reviews, 1939
  - Tall Story
    - Financial papers, 1959 See also Oversize
    - General correspondence, undated
    - Legal papers, 1959-1963, (2 folders)
    - Publicity, 1959-1960
    - Reviews, 1960
    - Working papers, 1960, undated
  - Theatre at Sea (Box 126)
    - Legal papers, 1976
    - Publicity, 1977
  - There Was a Little Girl
    - Casting, 1959-1960
    - Financial papers
      - General, 1959-1960
      - Statements, 1960
    - General correspondence, 1960
    - Legal papers, 1959-1960
    - Miscellany, 1960
    - Publicity, 1959-1960
    - Reviews, 1960
    - Working papers, 1959-1960
  - This Is the Army
    - Publicity, 1982
    - Reviews, undated
  - Tiger, Tiger, Burning Bright
    - General correspondence, 1962-1963
    - Legal papers, 1962
    - Publicity, 1962-1963
    - Reviews, 1962-1963
  - To See Ourselves
    - Legal papers, 1935
    - Publicity, 1935
    - Reviews, 1935
  - To Sit on a Horse See Container 97, As the Lady Said to the Sailor
  - A Toy for Carmen, publicity, 1959
  - Trick, publicity, 1979
  - Two for the Show, legal papers, 1940
  - University Players/Theatre Unit
    - Publicity, 1930-1932
    - Working papers, undated
  - The Warrior's Husband, legal papers, 1942
  - Weddin' Day
    - Casting, 1986-1987
    - General correspondence, 1986-1988
    - Legal papers, 1986-1987
    - Publicity, 1987
    - Reviews, 1987
    - Working papers, script, 1986-1988, undated
  - Whistling in the Dark, publicity, 1941
  - Why I Went Crazy
    - Casting, undated
    - General correspondence, 1969
    - Legal papers, 1969
    - Publicity, 1969
    - Reviews, 1969
    - Working papers, 1969, undated See also Oversize
  - Wish You Were Here
    - Casting, 1952-1953
    - Financial papers
      - Expenses
        - June 1952-May 1953
        - June 1953-May 1954 (Box 127)
      - Investors, 1951-1965
      - Royalties, 1952-1985, (3 folders)
      - Statements, 1952-1978, (2 folders)
      - Taxes, 1954-1955
    - General correspondence, 1951-1957
    - Legal papers, 1951-1977 (Box 128)
    - Miscellany, 1953
    - Other productions
      - Chicago, Ill., 1954-1955
      - Ice Capades, 1954
      - London, Eng., 1953-1954
    - Publicity, 1952, undated
    - Reviews, 1952
    - Tickets, 1952-1953, undated
    - Working papers
      - Performance, 1952, undated
    - Working papers
      - Script, 1953, undated
      - Technical, 1952-1954, undated See also Oversize
  - The Wisteria Trees
    - Financial papers
      - General, 1950
      - Investors, 1949-1950
      - Royalties, 1949-1955
      - Statements, 1950
    - General correspondence, 1950-1982, undated
    - Legal papers, 1949-1976
    - Other productions
      - City Center of Music and Drama, New York, N.Y., 1955, undated
      - Miscellany, 1954-1964
      - South Africa, 1955
      - The York Theatre Co., New York, N.Y., 1982
    - Publicity, 1950
    - Reviews, 1950
    - Working papers
      - Performance, 1950
      - Script, 1950, undated
      - Technical, 1949-1950
  - The World of Suzie Wong (Box 129)
    - Casting, 1958, undated
    - Financial papers, 1959-1965
    - Legal papers, 1963
    - Publicity, 1957-1960, undated
    - Reviews, undated
    - Working papers, script, undated
- Writings File, 1925-1988 (Box 129-179)
  Contracts, correspondence, drafts, newspaper clippings, notes, outlines, royalty statements, and typescripts pertaining to the writings of Joshua Logan and others.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of author and therein by type of material.
  - Alexander, Ronald, Relative Strangers, 1973 (Box 129)
  - Anderson, Doris, Mack Sennett film, 1949
  - Anderson, Maxwell, Ulysses Africanus, 1939
  - Arbuzov, Aleksei, Tody Stranstvii (The Years of Travelling), 1957
  - Atkin, Charles, Happily Ever After, 1976-1982
  - Axelrod, George
    - Act One, undated
    - Breakfast at Tiffany's, 1960
    - Bus Stop, 1956, undated (Box 130)
  - Barry, Julian, Escadrille, undated
  - Behrman, S. N.
    - The Cold Wind and the Warm, 1958
    - The Worcester Account, 1954
  - Benchley, Robert, Christmas Afternoon, undated
  - Benet, Stephen Vincent, The Sobbin' Women, undated
  - Benson, Sally, Meet Me in St. Louis, 1960-1986
  - Bobrick, Sam See Container 131, Clark, Ron
  - Boland, Bridget, Mistress Masham's Repose, draft screenplays, undated, (2 folders)
  - Bolton, Guy, Anything Goes, undated
  - Brean, Herbert
    - A Voice in the Matter, undated
    - Wilders Walk Away, 1970 (Box 131)
  - Brecht, Bertolt, The Threepenny Opera, 1951
  - Brennan, Richard H., A Treatment of a Film on Washington and the Revolutionary War Years, 1981-1982
  - Bullock, Walter, The Late Christopher Bean, 1952-1961 See also Container 133, Dinelli, Mel, and Container 137, Howard, Sidney
  - Caplin, Elliott A., Meegan's Game, 1975, undated
  - Capote, Truman, Breakfast at Tiffany's, undated
  - Chandler, Charlotte See Container 178, Stricklyn, Ray
  - Chandler, Sydney, Wentworth Hall, 1982
  - Churchill, Sir Winston (as subject of an untitled drama), undated
  - Clark, Ron, and Sam Bobrick, Murder! undated
  - Cohen, Larry, Motive, 1972 (Box 132)
  - Conrad, Charles J., The Third House, 1954
  - Conte, Ben, and Peter Heim, This Is Not a Musical Comedy, 1986
  - Cuzzani, Agustin, A Pound of Flesh, 1969
  - Daley, Ron, The Red Palace, 1980-1981
  - Dalrymple, Jean, and Nedda Harrigan, Destination Unknown
    - Manuscript draft, undated
      - Preservation photocopies, (2 folders)
      - Originals (fragile), (4 folders)
    - Typescript, (3 folders) (Box 133)
  - Davis, Owen, The Great Gatsby, undated
  - Dial, William, Shelley, 1971
  - Dickman, Paul Raymond, The First Christmas, 1983
  - Dinelli, Mel, Christopher Bean, 1955 See also Container 131, Bullock, Walter and Container 137, Howard, Sidney
  - Don Juan, 1964, undated
  - Drayton, Mary See Container 152, Logan, Joshua, Scripts, Careful! (He Might Hear You)
  - Dreifuss, Arthur, The Master Forger, 1964-1965, (2 folders)
  - Dunbar, Paul Laurence, A Death Song, undated
  - Epstein, Julius J., Fanny, 1959
  - Feibleman, Peter, A Place Without Twilight, undated, (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - Feld, Bruce, Duel, 1976
  - Fields, Herbert, Fifty Million Frenchmen, 1929
  - Flagstad, Sondra J., Lily, 1980-1982
  - Flynn, Don
    - The Black Sheep, 1974-1976
    - A Meaningful Relationship, 1976
  - Foster, Norman, Faust, 1975 (Box 135)
  - Franklin, Max, The Careful Man, undated
  - Friedman, Al, Game Man, undated
  - Friedman, Karl, No Balm in Gilead, 1974
  - Gaddis, Thomas E., Birdman of Alcatraz, 1957
  - The Girl Couldn't Help It, undated
  - Glassman, J. K., Judge Harlow's Daughter, 1981
  - Gluckman, Evelyn Crawford, Cliché, Touché, or the Woodstock Way, 1981
  - Gould, Barney, Goldrush Troupers, or Next Week: East Lynne, 1967-1982 (Box 136)
  - Grand Cane, undated
  - Haldane, Harry, A Different Time, undated
  - Harrigan, Edward, Cordelia's Aspirations, undated
  - Hart, Lorenz See Container 176, Rodgers, Richard
  - Hart, Moss, Jubilee! undated
  - Haynes, Lincoln, Midnight Soba, 1971, undated
  - Hecht, Ben, Charles MacArthur, and Charles Bruce Millholland, Twentieth Century, undated
  - Heim, Peter See Container 132, Conte, Ben
  - Herlihy, James Leo, and William Noble, Blue Denim, 1958
  - Helen of Troy, undated (Box 137)
  - Hojo, Hideshi, The Fox and the Flute Player, undated
  - Holms, John Pynchon, The Short Straw, undated
  - Horrigan, Jack, Children! Children! undated
  - Horvath, Joan, and Ethel Seldin-Schwartz, Mama Is Dating Again, 1971
  - Howard, Sidney, The Late Christopher Bean, 1932 See also Container 131, Bullock, Walter and Container 133, Dinelli, Mel, (2 folders)
  - Huddleston, Floyd, Brother Elwood and his Gospel Truck, undated
  - Inge, William, and William Marchant, The Dark at the Top of the Stairs, undated
  - Jones, Elinor, Colette, 1970
  - Kahn, Bernie, You'll Never Guess Who Died Today, [1972] (Box 138)
  - Kahn, E. J., Partners, [1955]
  - Karshner, Roger, Monkey's Uncle, 1975
  - Kober, Arthur, Having a Wonderful Time, undated
  - Korneichuk, Aleksandr, Platon Krechet, 1957
  - Krasna, Norman, Kind Sir, 1952
  - Lamkin, Speed, and Eva Wolas, Out by the Country Club, 1956, undated
  - Learning, Mrs., untitled history of Mansfield, La., 1986
  - Lees, Gene, Wild, undated
  - Leontovich, Eugenie, and Suzanne Simon McAndrews, Father, Son and the Siren, 1984
  - Linney, Romulus, The Sorrows of Frederick the Great, 1966
  - Lockwood, Ellen See Containers 152-153, Logan, Joshua, Scripts, Careful! (He Might Hear You)
  - Logan, Joshua (Box 139)
    - Articles
      - Alcoholics Anonymous Story, 1961
      - Am I Directing Marlon Brando, 1987, undated
      - American theater, 1961
      - The Art in Yourself, 1953
      - Asiatic theater, undated
      - Behrman, S. N., souvenir program, undated
      - Can Marilyn Monroe Really Act? 1956
      - Can One Fall in Love with a Street? 1961
      - Christina Rossetti, 1930
      - Culver Military Academy, Culver, Ind., 1961-1965
      - Directing, 1952-1969, undated
      - Directing South Pacific, 1987
      - Drama in the Streets, undated
      - Everywoman, 1965-1966
      - Frank Sinatra, [1985]
      - Heggen, Thomas, 1966-1967, undated
      - The High Kicking Nuns of Japan, 1957
      - Hotel Room Scene, undated
      - How We Did South Pacific, 1987, undated
      - If It Must Be So--Sayonara, 1957
      - Interrelations between cinema and theater, 1959
      - Irving Berlin, 1978
      - The Jenkins Boys, 1960
      - John Crosby, 1961
      - Kilgallen, Dorothy, guest columnist for, [1961]
      - Leland Hayward, 1971
      - List of writings, 1969
      - The London Coliseum Production of Mister Roberts, undated
      - The Magic World of the Stage Director, undated
      - Making South Pacific, 1949, undated
      - Moscow Art Theatre, Moscow, USSR, 1973 (Box 140)
      - Moscow Revisited, 1958
      - My Invasion of Marseille, 1961
      - My Story, undated
      - Oh, You're Giving a Party for Chairs! undated
      - Paul Gauguin's The Nativity, 1975
      - Questions and Answers About The Wisteria Trees, undated
      - Reader's Digest Condensed Books, 1964
      - Remaking a Legend, 1961
      - Remaking Picnic, 1955
      - Rome, Harold, souvenir program, undated
      - Rules of Playwriting--Maxwell Anderson, 1984, undated
      - Sayonara, 1955
      - The Seamless Web, undated
      - Shows that appeal to soldiers, undated
      - Stanislavsky, Konstantin, undated
      - Theatre Must Evoke Emotions, undated
      - Theatregoing in Japan, undated
    - Books
      - The Black Art of Compromise, draft, undated
      - I'm Nobody, Who Are You?
        - Draft, 1964-1965, undated
        - Revised version, [1964]
      - Josh: My Up and Down, In and Out Life
        - Contract, 1972
        - Correspondence, 1971-1980, (2 folders)
        - Outlines and notes, 1973, undated
        - Drafts
          - 1970-1971
          - Pre-1972, (2 folders)
          - 1972 (Box 141)
            - Chapters 1-2, (2 folders)
            - Chapters 7-16, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 142)
            - Chapter 17
          - 1972-1973
            - Chapters 3-14, (7 folders)
            - Chapters 15-17, (2 folders) (Box 143)
          - 1973
            - Chapters 1-6, 16, (7 folders)
            - Chapters 17-23, (4 folders) (Box 144)
            - Nedda Logan recollection
            - Importance of sex
          - 1974
            - Chapters 1-5, (5 folders)
            - Chapters 6-8, (3 folders) (Box 145)
          - 1975
            - Chapters 9-17, (9 folders)
            - Chapter 18 (Box 146)
        - Miscellaneous pages, [1975], undated, (2 folders)
        - Photographs, photocopies of, 1975
        - Promotion, 1976
        - Reviews, 1976, (2 folders)
        - Royalty statements, 1975-1984
        - British edition, 1975-1977, undated
      - Miscellaneous
        - Sept. 1961-May 1977
        - June 1977-Oct. 1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 147)
      - Movie Stars, Real People, and Me
        - Correspondence, 1975-1978
        - Outline, 1977
        - Drafts, 1972-1977, undated, (13 folders); (11 folders) (Box 148)
        - Notes, 1977, undated
        - Promotion, 1978
        - Reviews, 1978
      - Or Not; The Confusing Life of the Theatre, draft, 1985
    - Forewords and introductions, 1941-1960, 1987, undated
    - Interviews
      - Columbia University, New York, N.Y., oral history
        - Correspondence, 1980
        - Interview (transcript), 1981*, * Item may not be photocopied; (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 149)
      - KBOY-FM, Medford, Oreg., 1968
      - Miscellaneous, 1958-1985
      - Not For Women Only, undated
    - Lectures, 1984
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1983, 1987, undated
    - Novels
      - Flying Wing on the Great White Leader, draft, 1963
      - Should Auld Acquaintance Be Forgot, draft, 1980
      - Untitled, 1978-1979
    - Poetry, 1926-1986, undated
    - Proposed books (Box 150)
      - Etcetera, 1981
      - Nowhere to Go But Up, 1984
      - Showmanship, 1977, 1980, 1987
    - Reviews, 1959-1987, undated
    - Scripts
      - Admiral [Matthew Calbraith] Perry Story, 1955
      - As the Lady Said to the Sailor..., 1972, undated
      - Blue Star, 1961
      - Careful! (He Might Hear You)
        - Coauthor, Nedda Logan
          - Drafts
            - Nov. 1967-Feb. 1968, (4 folders)
            - Feb. 1968-July 1970, (8 folders) (Box 151)
            - Jan. 1971-circa 1972, (2 folders) (Box 152)
          - Miscellaneous pages, 1968
          - Notes, 1969-1970, undated
        - Other authors and titles
          - Drayton, Mary, undated
          - Lockwood, Ellen
            - P.S. (A Postscript to a Ridiculous Life), 1967, (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box 153)
            - The Piano Boat, 1967-1968, (3 folders)
          - Pressburger, Emeric, Postscript to a Ridiculous Life, 1966
        - Other titles (Box 154)
          - The Empress of Halifax, 1978
          - The Listener, 1964
          - Oh Vanessa! undated
      - Carmen
        - French version, 1962
        - Master score, undated, (2 folders)
        - Moscow Art Theatre, Moscow, USSR, 1925
      - Carmen and the Corporal
        - Draft, 1981
        - Corrected pages, 1982
        - Dialogues, 1981
        - Miscellaneous pages, 1981-1982, undated (Box 155)
        - Songs and scenes, 1979-1981, (3 folders)
      - Carnaby Street, 1966
      - Charley's Aunt, 1981, undated, (3 folders)
      - Cherry
        - Draft, 1972-1973, undated, (2 folders) (Box 156)
        - Final version, undated
        - Miscellaneous pages, 1972, undated
        - Promotion, 1973
      - Cuba Libra
        - Correspondence, 1940-1953, undated
        - Background material, 1943-1950, undated
        - Outlines, 1949-1955, undated
        - Notes, undated, (3 folders)
      - Escadrille, undated (Box 157)
      - Fanny, 1983-1984, undated, (3 folders)
      - Harrigan and Hart See Containers 165-166, Mulligan Guards
      - Huck and Jim on the Mississippi
        - Early versions
          - Huck and Jim
            - Draft, circa 1950, (2 folders)
            - Miscellaneous pages and notes, circa 1950
          - Raft on the River, 1950
        - Drafts, 1983-1986, (2 folders); (9 folders); (8 folders) (Box 158, Box 159)
        - Miscellaneous pages, 1982-1987, undated, (3 folders); (10 folders) (Box 160)
        - Lyrics, 1987, undated
        - Notes, 1983-1987, undated
      - I Remember Mama, 1985
      - Jonathan Wild (Box 161)
        - Correspondence, 1985-1986
        - Draft, 1985-1986, undated, (3 folders)
        - Other titles
          - Great Jonathan, 1971, (3 folders)
          - Jonathan the Great, 1971, (2 folders) (Box 162)
          - The Life of Jonathan Wild The Great, undated
      - Lysistrata, 1978, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miss Moffat
        - Correspondence, 1972-1974
        - Drafts, 1972-1978, (3 folders); (6 folders); (1folder) (Box 163, Box 164)
        - Miscellaneous pages, 1972-1974, (10 folders); (6 folders) (Box 165)
        - Stage manager's playing version, 1974, (2 folders)
        - Synopsis, 1974
      - Mister Roberts, 1948, undated
      - Mulligan Guards
        - Draft, undated
        - Miscellaneous pages, 1977, undated (Box 166)
        - Synopsis, undated
        - Other titles
          - The Mulligan Guards' Ball, undated
          - The Mulligan Guards Forever, 1977